zona-musical.com 2008-12-17

# Zona-Musical Privacy Policy

Last Revised December 20, 2006

In addition to reviewing this privacy policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of zona-musical.com ("Website") constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions. 

This policy does not cover information collected on sites linked to from the Website. 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

It is the goal of our Website to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site. 

THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS 

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. 

HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU 

Service Provider uses information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our publications, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the publication. Similarly, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

We may share e-mail addresses and sell or share all other information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail. 

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share anonymous and personal data about our users for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

COOKIES 

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver dynamic content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies. 

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don't want any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly. 

IP ADDRESS 

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website. 

KIDS AND PARENTS 

This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 18. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. 

If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at zona.musical.com@gmail.com. 

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator. We welcome your feedback.
